I could be killing,
I could be stealing but no.
Today I decided to create 1 new idea.
Day 6
I'm going for another 1.
Hi sorry all right?
I call Caio.
I am a BG researcher doing research on anxiety and stress.
I swear there are two questions.
Quickly take your time.
What is the name Alexandre and cs believe that
nowadays Brazilians are more stressed.
Yes OR no?
I'm from IBGE institute 1 company here develops medications including
1 New medication has already been approved by Anvisa that reduces stress
by up to eighty-five percent on PMS and also controls anxiety.
I brought a girl to show you.
This is the medicine of happiness
palm face,
right?
He knows how to sell the expensive product for only twelve reais,
all made with love.
And here's the guys research there's nothing written.
Oh thanks guys,
that's all.
See an institute that we do research to feel brands in the market.
This is the medicine of happiness.
For only twelve reais.
This medicine will combat your anxiety decrease
your friend's TPM control train.
And here's your satisfaction research.
James takes a look here.
O.